### GoVenus Inc. Privacy Policy

Last updated: July 25, 2017

GOVENUS WEBSITE PRIVACY POLICY ("PRIVACY POLICY") APPLIES TO HOW WE COLLECT, USE AND PROCESS YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION WHEN YOU USE THE GOVENUS SOFTWARE APPLICATION AND/OR WEBSITE ("WEBSITE"). PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. PLEASE NOTE IN PARTICULAR THE PARTS THAT ARE IN BOLD WRITING AS THESE PARTS MIGHT LIMIT OUR RISK OR LIABILITY, REQUIRE YOU TO INDEMNIFY US OR TO ASSUME RISK AND LIABILITY FOR CERTAIN ISSUES, OR TO ACKNOWLEDGE CERTAIN FACTS.

1\. Scope of the Privacy Policy

1.1 Introduction and scope

1.2 Heavenly Concepts Pty Ltd ("GoVenus" or "we" or "us" or "our") offers an online relationship service, using primarily the ancient art of astrology to help you find a suitable matching potential partner (the "Service"). The Service allows you to find information on an individual's astrological profile, based on their date, time (where provided) and place of birth. It also allows you to register to receive matching members' details, and for you to share your astrological profile with matching members. You can then see more information about that member as well as have a basic chat or block that member.

1.2.1 This GoVenus Website Privacy Policy (this "Privacy Policy"), which must be read together with our Website Terms and Conditions at https://www.govenus.co/tandc.html ("Terms"), sets out what we will do with any Personal Information (defined in paragraph 2.1 below) we collect from or about you, or that you provide to us, when you use the Website. Unless defined elsewhere, terms in this Privacy Policy shall bear the same meaning ascribed to them in the Terms.

1.2.2 Please read this Privacy Policy carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your Personal Information and how we will treat it.

1.2.3 GoVenus is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. We strive to ensure that our use of your Personal Information is lawful, reasonable, and relevant to our business activities, with the ultimate goal of improving our Services and your experience.

1.3 Your consent to the processing of your personal information on the terms and conditions set out in this Privacy Policy

1.3.1 By agreeing to this Privacy Policy, you provide us with your express consent and agreement that we may collect, get, receive, record, organise, collate, store, update, change, retrieve, read, process, use and share your Personal Information in the ways set out in this Privacy Policy. When we do one or more of these actions with your Personal Information, we are "Processing" your Personal Information.

1.3.2 If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, or are concerned about any aspect as it relates to your Personal Information, please do not continue to use the Website and the Services.

1.4 Who does this Privacy Policy apply to?

1.4.1 This Privacy Policy applies to-

1.4.1.1 us, and our successors-in-title; and

1.4.1.2 you, namely a person who:

1.4.1.2.1 browses, uses, accesses, refers to, views and/or downloads the information made available by us on the Website ("Content") for whatever purpose; and/or

1.4.1.2.2 registers as a user on the Website by creating a user Account,

regardless of the device which you use to access it, which device is capable of using or enabled to use the Website, including but not limited to internet-connected computer, mobile devices and tablets ("Access Device"), ("user", "you", or "your").

1.4.2 This Privacy Policy does not apply to other parties' websites, products or services, such as websites linked to, from or advertised on the Website, or websites which link to or advertise the Website.

2\. What is Personal Information?

2.1 "Personal Information" refers to private information about an identifiable person, which includes your name and surname, age, date, time and place of birth, contact details (e.g. your home address, postal address, e-mail address or phone number), physical location, social media account details and profile pictures.

3\. How do we receive your Personal Information?

3.1 We may receive your Personal Information in several ways, including, when (i) you access, browse or make use of Website and/or the Content on the Website; (ii) you create / register a user account on the Website to access or make use of the Services; (iii) you contact us, by email or telephonically, with any queries; (iv) we carry out demographic research; and/or (v) you submit your Personal Information to us for any other reason, or authorise third parties to do so.

3.2 We passively receive some of your Personal Information from the Access Device that you use to access and navigate through the Website, using various technological means, including relying on server logs to collect and maintain log file information.

3.3 We also use cookies and anonymous identifiers which enable our computer system to recognise you as a unique user when you visit the Website. A cookie is a small text file (including an alphanumeric identifier) which our computer system transfers to your Access Device through your web browser when you visit the Website and which is stored via your web browser. When you visit the Website again, the cookie allows the site to recognise your browser. Cookies may store user preferences and other information.

You may disable the use of cookies by configuring your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do so, you may not be able to enjoy all of the features and functionality of the Website.

3.4 Some of the information we receive is Personal Information, and some is non-personal information that becomes personal if it is connected to your account information. In some circumstances we will de-identify, anonymise or segregate information so that we may make use of it in aggregate form without treating it as Personal Information.

4\. What information do we receive?

4.1 Other information which might be “Personal Information” that we receive may include:

4.1.1 "Basic Account Information": To register a user account on the Website, you must provide (i) an e-mail address, name, surname, contact details, physical location (to match you to similarly located users), your date and place of birth, and preferably the time of your birth and (ii) transaction-related information (including credit card details) for purposes of making purchases, responding to any offers, or downloading or using applications from us. If you do not wish to provide Basic Account Information to us, then you will not be able to register a user account or to use the Services on the Website.

4.1.1.1 Volunteering any other information beyond Basic Account Information is optional. Most of GoVenus' features also require additional information to function, as described below. If you do not agree to share other information with us, then you may not be able to enjoy all of the features and functionality on the Website.

4.1.2 "Other Account Information": date of birth, gender, profile picture(s), physical location, full contact details, interests, likes and preferences, relationship interests, photos, personal description, and other information you may be asked to provide from time to time as part of your Account.

4.1.3 “Device and Device event information”: Your IP address, unique device identifier, the nature of the Access Device which you used to access the Website (e.g. a computer, tablet or smart phone, and which type thereof), the geographic location from which you accessed our Website (i.e. the geographic location of your Access Device), hardware model and settings, operating system type and version, browser language, system activity, crashes.

4.1.4 “Log information”: When you use the Website, we may automatically collect and store certain information in server logs (i.e. our web servers automatically record and maintain a log of their activities when users access the Website), which may include your “site activity information”, such as details of how, when and for how long you accessed the Website, what links you went to, what Content you accessed, the amount of Content viewed and the order of that Content and the amount of time spent on the specific Content.

4.1.5 "Profile information": We may create a profile about you that will be linked to your user Account. We may process information and usage data to make targeted recommendations to you when you are logged in to the Website.

4.1.6 “Location information”: We may use various technologies to determine your actual location, such as geographical data from your Access Device (which is usually based on the GPS or IP location).

4.1.7 "Children": the Website is not targeted at individuals under the age of majority in the relevant jurisdiction. We do not knowingly allow persons in this age group to create accounts or use our Services without permission to do so, nor collect, maintain, or use Personal Information from children under the age of majority in the relevant jurisdiction.

5\. How do we use your Personal Information?

5.1 We may use your Personal information to:

5.1.1 create your user Account and ensure that it doesn't duplicate an existing user account on the Website, and allow use of the Website and Services;

5.1.2 as a registered user, establish, verify or authenticate your identity when you view and access the Website;

5.1.3 maintain and update our user databases;

5.1.4 diagnose and deal with technical issues and customer support queries and other user queries, such as problems with our server, determine the optimal and fastest route for your Access Device to use in connecting with the Website, and administer, maintain and secure the Website;

5.1.5 detect, prevent or deal with actual or alleged fraud, security or the abuse, misuse or unauthorised use of the Website and/or contravention of this Privacy Policy;

5.1.6 conduct market research surveys, product research and development;

5.1.7 provide you with the latest information about our Services, subject to your communications preferences;

5.1.8 to communicate with you and maintain records of our communications with you, including to inform you about any changes to the Website, our Services, our Terms, this Privacy Policy or other changes that are relevant to you;

5.1.9 compile non-personal statistical information about browsing habits, click patterns and access to the Website;

5.1.10 improve the Website, analyse trends and administer the Website, including requesting feedback on Content and the Services;

5.1.11 fulfil any contractual obligations we may have to you or any third party;

5.1.12 improve your user experience and the overall quality of our Services;

5.1.13 customise the Website to your preferences and tailor information and/or Content for you to ensure that it is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your Access Device;

5.1.14 to compile and use statistical information about you and other users and their access to and use of the Website, browsing habits, click-patterns, preferences, and demographics which we may use to develop, provide and improve the Website, including, recommendations to users and tailoring information and Content for users.

5.1.14.1 Please note that the information referred to in the above paragraph is aggregate information about our users that has been de-identified such that it cannot reasonably be linked back by a third party to identify a user individually;

5.1.15 for security, administrative and legal purposes;

5.1.16 for customer relations; and

5.1.17 other activities not specifically mentioned which are lawful, reasonable, relevant to our business activities and the minimum necessary and adequate in order for us to provide the Website and our Services.

6\. Sharing of Personal Information

6.1 We will not intentionally disclose your Personal Information to third parties other than as set out in this Privacy Policy below or with your permission.

6.2 When you register as a user of GoVenus, your GoVenus profile will be viewable by other users of the Service. Other users will be able to view information you have provided to us directly, such as your photos, your first name, your age and birth date, your personal description, and information you have in common with the person viewing your profile.

6.3 In addition to 6.2 above, if you have created a user account and are a registered user of our Services, in order to provide our Services, we may share the Personal Information contained in your user profile with other GoVenus registered users, with whom you are a "match".

6.4 You agree that your Personal Information may be shared under the following circumstances:

6.4.1 to our agents, advisers, service providers and suppliers who have agreed to be bound by this Privacy Policy;

6.4.2 to our employees, contractors and agents if and to the extent that they need to know that information in order to process it for us and/or to provide services for or to us, such as site hosting, development and administration, technical support (only in respect of the Website) and other support services. We will authorise any information processing done by a third party on our behalf, amongst other things by entering into written agreements with those third parties governing our relationship with them and containing confidentiality and non-disclosure provisions. Such persons may be disciplined, their contracts terminated or other appropriate action taken if they fail to meet their obligations;

6.4.3 in order to enforce or apply the Terms or any other contract between you and us;

6.4.4 in order to protect our rights, property or safety or that of our users, employees, contractors, agents and any other third party;

6.4.5 in order to mitigate any actual or reasonably perceived risk to us, our users, employees, contractors, agents or any other third party;

6.4.6 to any third party who acquires (or proposes to acquire) ownership or control of our assets, shares or management, or that of our affiliates, and/or the Website, whether by sale, merger, acquisition or otherwise, and/or to any third party from who we acquire (or propose to acquire) ownership or control of assets, shares or management, whether by purchase, merger, acquisition or otherwise, subject to confidentiality provisions consistent with this Privacy Policy;

6.4.7 to governmental agencies, stock exchanges and other regulatory or self-regulatory bodies if we are required to do so by law or if we reasonably believe that such action is necessary to:

6.4.7.1 comply with the law or with any legal process;

6.4.7.2 protect and defend the rights, property or safety of us, our affiliates or our clients, employees, contractors and agents or any third party;

6.4.7.3 detect, prevent or deal with actual or alleged fraud, security or technical issues or the abuse, misuse or unauthorised use of our Website and/or contravention of this Privacy Policy;

6.4.7.4 protect the rights, property or safety of members of the public (if you provide false or deceptive information about yourself or misrepresent yourself as being someone else, we may proactively disclose such information to the appropriate regulatory bodies and/or commercial entities).

6.5 We may use your Personal Information to compile profiles for statistical purposes and may freely trade with such profiles and statistical data, provided that the profiles or statistical data cannot be linked back to you by a third party.

6.6 We will get your permission before disclosing your Personal Information to any third party for any other purpose.

7\. Security

7.1 Although absolute security cannot be guaranteed on the Internet, we take reasonable technical and organisational measures to secure the integrity of retained information, using accepted technological standards to prevent unauthorised access to or disclosure of your Personal Information, and protect your Personal Information from misuse, loss, alteration or destruction.

7.2 We usually use encrypted servers to store all the Personal Information that we collect and such servers are either on our premises or on third party locations in jurisdictions which may not have comparable data protection legislation.

7.3 From time to time, we review our information collection, storage and processing practices, including physical security measures, to keep up to date with good practice.

7.4 We also create a back-up for operational and safety purposes.

7.5 Refer to paragraph 6.4.2 regarding measures to protect the information which is provided to employees, agents and contractors on a need-to-know basis.

7.6 Even by taking the above measures when Processing Personal Information, we do not guarantee that your Personal Information is 100% secure.

8\. Storage and transfer of your Personal Information

8.1 We store your Personal Information on our servers.

8.2 We reserve the right to transfer to and/or store your Personal Information on servers in a jurisdiction other than where it was collected, and such jurisdiction may not have comparable data protection legislation.

8.3 If the location that Personal Information is transferred to does not have substantially similar laws which provide for the protection of Personal Information, we will take reasonably practicable steps to ensure that your Personal Information is adequately protected in that jurisdiction.

9\. Data retention

9.1 We may retain all Personal Information that we collect from you as long as it remains necessary for the purposes for which it was collected unless there is a valid technical, legal or business reason for us to delete, destroy or de-identify it.

9.2 Further, we may keep some or all of your Personal Information for as long as we are required by law, a code of conduct or we reasonably need it for lawful purposes related to our functions and activities; we reasonably need it for evidentiary purposes; or you agree to us keeping it for a specified period.

9.3 If you do not access the Website for a consecutive period of two and a half years we will inform you that your Account is dormant; and if you do not access the Website for a further six months after the dormancy notification, we will delete, destroy or de-identify all your Personal Information from our records, except for information which we store for historical, statistical or research purposes.

10\. Keeping your Personal Information updated and correct

10.1 To the extent required by law, we will take steps to ensure that your Personal Information is accurate, complete, not misleading, and up to date having regard to the purpose for which the information was collected or used.

10.2 You must let us know if you believe any information we have about you is incorrect, incomplete, misleading or out of date. If you are a registered user of the Website, you can modify some of the Personal Information you have included in your profile by logging in and accessing your Account.

10.3 You may request that your Personal Information be deleted if it is no longer required for the purposes for which it was collected or required by us in terms of any applicable law.

11\. Direct marketing

11.1 When you register on the Website you will receive marketing communications from us.

11.2 You may refuse to accept, require us to discontinue, or pre-emptively block any approach or communications from us if that approach or communication is primarily for the purpose of direct marketing (“direct marketing communications”).

11.3 You may opt out of receiving direct marketing communications from us at any time by requesting us (in any manner, whether telephonically, electronically, in writing or in person) to desist from initiating any direct marketing to you.

11.4 If you have opted out, we may send you written (which may include electronic writing) confirmation of receipt of your opt out request, and not send you any further direct marketing communications.

12\. Your controls

12.1 Information you provide about yourself while using our Service: We provide areas on our Service where you can post information about yourself and others and communicate with others. Such postings are governed by our Terms. In instances where you voluntarily disclose Personal Information on publicly-viewable pages, that information will be publicly available and can be collected and used by others. For example, if you post your email address on a publicly-viewable page, you may receive unsolicited messages. We cannot control who reads your public posts or what other users may do with the information you voluntarily post. We therefore encourage you to exercise discretion and caution with respect to your Personal Information.

12.2 You should remember that you have basic rights and responsibilities with respect to your Personal Information. For example, you may:

12.2.1 control who you share information with, on or via the Website;

12.2.2 set your browser to block all cookies, including cookies associated with our Services, or to indicate when a cookie is being sent by us;

12.2.3 request that we indicate to you what Personal Information of yours we have on our systems, subject to legal requirements;

12.2.4 request that we correct or update your Personal Information or to destroy or delete your Personal Information, subject to legal requirements;

12.2.5 object to any unlawful processing of your Personal Information; and

12.2.6 refuse the processing of your Personal Information for direct marketing purposes (see above).

12.3 As far as the law allows, we may charge a fee for attending to any of your requests above and/or provide a reason why we cannot accommodate the request.

13\. Third party sites

13.1 We are not responsible for the privacy practices of a third party site to which there may be a link on the Website or any Content on the Website.

13.2 We advise you to read the privacy policy of each website which you visit and to determine your privacy settings in accordance with your personal preferences.

14\. Changes to this Privacy Policy

14.1 From time to time, we may revise this Privacy Policy to reflect company initiatives, changes in the law or technology or changes in our practices regarding the Processing and use of Personal Information. You agree to review the Privacy Policy whenever you visit the Website for any such amendments. Save as expressly provided to the contrary in this Privacy Policy, the amended version of the Privacy Policy shall supersede and replace all previous versions thereof.

14.2 We will not use or disclose Personal Information provided to us pursuant to this Privacy Policy in ways other than the ones described above, without informing you and providing you with the opportunity to consent to such modified conditions concerning the use and disclosure of your Personal Information.

15\. CPA, POPI and other laws

15.1 If this Privacy Policy or any provision in this Privacy Policy is regulated by or subject to consumer protection laws, data privacy laws or any other applicable laws in your jurisdiction, it is not intended that any provision of this Privacy Policy contravenes any such laws. Therefore all provisions of this Privacy Policy must be treated as being qualified, to the extent necessary, to ensure that the provisions of such laws are complied with.

15.2 No provision of this Privacy Policy:

15.2.1 does or purports to limit or exempt us from any liability (including, without limitation, for any loss directly or indirectly attributable to our gross negligence or wilful default or that of any other person acting for or controlled by us) to the extent that the law does not allow such a limitation or exemption;

15.2.2 requires you to assume risk or liability for the kind of liability or loss, to the extent that the law does not allow such an assumption of risk or liability; or

15.2.3 limits or excludes any warranties or obligations which are implied into this Privacy Policy by applicable laws, to the extent that the law does not allow them to be limited or excluded.

16\. Governing law

16.1 The contents of this Privacy Policy shall be governed by South African law.

16.2 If any provision of this Privacy Policy is judged to be illegal, void or unenforceable due to applicable law or by order of a court of a competent jurisdiction it shall be deemed deleted and the continuation in full force and effect of the remainder of the provisions will not be prejudiced.

17\. How can I contact GoVenus?

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy please feel free to contact us at privacy@govenus.co.

About us

Ts & Cs

Our [Terms and Conditions](https://www.govenus.co/tandc.html) of use of our site.

Found a bug?

Open a [new issue](https://www.govenus.co/gvTicket.html) if you suspect a bug.

* * *

© **Heavenly Concepts Pty Ltd.**
